恭喜疯狂派对
congratulations crazy party
felicitaciones partido de locos
再来一个标题，告诉我你对这个在短时间内取得了巨大成就的非凡团队的感受。
One more title, tell me your feelings about this extraordinary group that in a short time has achieved a lot.
Un título más, contame tus sentimientos de este extraordinario grupo que en poco tiempo ha logrado muchísimo.
嗯，为这个团队感到高兴，高兴，事实是我们已经说过了，我想我在今年年初就告诉过你了。
Well, happy, happy for this group, the truth is that we said it, I think I told you at the beginning of the year.
Bueno, contento, contento por este grupo, la verdad que lo dijimos, creo que te lo dije a vos al principio de año.
我们知道这是一个与此作斗争的团体，我们从一开始就负责。
We knew it was a group to fight this and we took charge from the beginning.
que sabíamos que era un grupo para pelear esto y nos hicimos cargo desde el principio.
我们有球员可以做到这一点，而且做得很好，事实是我们很高兴实现第一个目标
We have the players to do it and well, the truth is that we are happy to achieve the first objective
tenemos jugadores como para hacerlo y bueno la verdad que feliz de conseguir el primer objetivo
现在想想接下来会发生什么。
and now think about what's coming.
y ya pensar en lo que se viene.
今天是我们认识的一个非常难对付的对手。
Today was a very tough opponent that we knew.
Hoy fue un rival muy duro que sabíamos.
他们是最后一个冠军，最后一个联赛冠军，他们也参加了另一场决赛，他们是一支伟大的球队，非常好。
They are the last champion, the last champion of the League, they played in the other final as well, they are a great team, very good.
Es el último campeón, el último campeón de la Liga, jugó la otra final también, es un granísimo equipo, muy bien.
工作得很好，很好，少了一个，我们就遭受了一次，我们又遭受了一次，直到最后，这表明了这支球队的实力
very well worked and good with one less we suffered with one more we suffered until the end and it shows what this team is
muy bien trabajado y bueno con uno menos sufrimos con uno más nosotros sufrimos hasta el final y demuestra lo que es este equipo
里奥，这支球队的特点是什么，在如此短的时间内从根本上改变了俱乐部的历史？
And what is the characteristic, Leo, of this group that in such a short time radically transformed the history of this club?
¿Y cuál es la característica, Leo, de este grupo que en tan poco tiempo transformó radicalmente la historia de este club?
他们可以在这样的情况下获得这个冠军，并成为美国职业足球大联盟常规赛中最好的球队。
and they can come to scenarios like this and take this title and be the best team in Major League Soccer in the regular season.
y puede venir a escenarios como este y llevarse este título y ser el mejor equipo de la Mayor League Soccer en la temporada regular.
我认为泰特美术馆的到来以及我们到达时我也认为......
I think that the arrival of the Tate and when we arrived I also think that...
Yo creo que la llegada del Tate y cuando fuimos llegando nosotros también creo que...
这个想法很明确，从一开始就想成为主角，想要控球，想要通过……寻找对手。
that the idea was clear of wanting to be the protagonist from the beginning, of wanting to have the ball, of looking for rivals through...
que la idea fue clara de querer ser protagonista desde el principio, de querer tener la pelota, de buscar los rivales a través de...
游戏的一部分，然后重要的球员来到我们身边，这使得......
of the game, then important players came to us that made...
del juego, después nos llegaron jugadores importantes que eso hizo que...
球队从比赛、个性和竞争中成长得更多。
that the team grows much more from the game, from the personality, from competing.
que el equipo crezca mucho más del juego, de la personalidad, de competir.
我们试图消除所有游戏的竞争。
We try to decompetite all the games.
Intentamos descompetir todos los partidos.
正如我所说，不久前，我们在联赛杯中表现出色，但我们却缺席了。
As I said, not long ago, we competed very well in the League Cup and we were missing.
Como decía, no hace mucho, competimos muy bien en la League Cup y nos faltaban.
许多球员在这一年中也遭受了很多伤病，我们无法全部在一起。
Many players also had many injuries throughout the year where we couldn't all be together.
muchos jugadores también durante todo el año tuvimos muchas lesiones donde no pudimos estar todos juntos.
几乎从来没有，在很短的时间内，整个团队都聚集在一起，由于某种原因，这没有发生。
almost never, in a very short time the whole group was together, for one reason or another it didn't happen.
casi nunca, en muy poco tiempo estuvimos todo el grupo juntos, por una cosa u otra no se daba.
小组正在玩非常艰苦的游戏。
and the group was playing very hard games.
y el grupo fue sacando partidos muy duros.
我们有美洲杯。
We had the Copa América.
Tuvimos la Copa América.
我认为还有五场客场比赛，我们对阵的是非常强悍的对手，他们都是顶级的。
I think there were five games away and we played against very tough rivals who were fighting at the top.
Creo que fueron cinco partidos fuera y jugamos contra rivales muy duros que estaban peleando arriba.
结果非常积极，很好地表明了这个团队的实力。
and the results were very positive and well that shows what this team is.
y los resultados fueron muy positivos y bueno eso demuestra lo que es este equipo.
最后的。
Last.
Última.
另一部分会改变芯片，你必须全力以赴。
Another part comes along that changes the chip and you have to go for everything.
viene otra parte que cambia el chip y hay que ir por todo.
球队准备好参加美国职业足球大联盟杯并创造支持率纪录了吗？
How is the team ready to go for the MLS Cup and to also set the record in the Supportership.
cómo está el equipo para ir a buscar la MLS Cup y para hacer también el récord en el Supportership.
我认为记录是次要的，尽管我们也有很好的机会载入史册。
I think the record is secondary, although we have a nice opportunity to go down in history in that too.
Creo que el récord es secundario, si bien tenemos una linda oportunidad para quedar en la historia en eso también.
我认为至少第一个目标已经实现，现在考虑即将发生的事情并不是第一个目标
I think that the least the first objective has been achieved and now to think about what is coming is not the first
creo que lo de menos el primer objetivo está cumplido y ahora pensar en lo que lo que se viene no el primero es
虽然是三人，但这是一场可能发生的比赛。
It's three, but then it's a game that can happen.
es a tres, pero después a un partido que puede pasar.
无论如何，我们有一个很大的优势，我们打所有的主场比赛，这就是
anything but we have a great advantage that we play all the home games and that was what
cualquier cosa pero tenemos una gran ventaja que jugamos todos los partidos de local y que era lo que
我们正在寻找什么，我认为作为当地人，我们非常......
What we were looking for, I think that as locals we are very...
Lo que buscábamos, creo que nosotros de local somos muy...
非常强大，当他出去在任何体育场踢球时。
very strong and when he went out to play in any stadium.
muy fuerte y cuando salía a jugar a cualquier estadio.
AMLS 并不容易，我认为作为本地人，我们...
The AMLS is not easy and I think that being local we have...
El AMLS no es fácil y nosotros creo que siendo locales tenemos...
一个巨大的优势，然后你必须证明它。
a great advantage and then you have to prove it.
una gran ventaja y después hay que demostrarlo.
谢谢，莱昂。
Thanks, Leon.
Gracias, León.
与团队一起享受。
Enjoy with the team.
Disfruta con el equipo.